Christopher Nelson

Software Developer

Objective

A software developer with 2+ years experience looking to grow with a company. Able to create websites while following strict W3C standards as well as a solid understanding of Android SDK. Has a high awareness of industry issues and trends; particularly in regard to accessibility, usability, and emerging technologies.

Experience

Freelance Software Developer July 2016 - Present

- Freelance Web Developer, Orlando, FL
 - Build Websites
 - · Promote and Market Services
 - Submit Invoices and Collect Payment
 - Find and Manage Clients
- Android Developer, Orlando, FL.

Nerro Notes, Android Application - (In Development)

https://github.com/cmfnels/Nerro

- Design UI for android application
- Debug and Test Application for Optimal performance.
- Work with the Android SDK.
- Write Code using Java

Front-End Developer September 2017 - December 2017

P.A. Distributions, Woodland Park, CO

- Designed, modified and implemented Wordpress & Magento themes
- Maintained and built WooCommerce webpages
- Worked with SQL Databases
- Cleaned and optimized legacy code
- Tested sites and fixed bugs within software
- Developed and implemented SEO strategies to further companies sales

Facility Manager December 2015 - December 2017

Cathedral Pines, Monument, CO

- Oversaw lodge events
- Collected rental fees
- Light maintenance of the facility
- Maintained a safe environment for guests

Relief Manager July 2015 - September 2017

Front Range Self Storage, Monument, CO

- Received payments from tenants
- Maintained and supervised property
- Rented units to new tenets
- Reviewed policies and procedures with new tenants
- Filed paperwork and process reports

Projects

Wed Developer Volunteer

Pikes Peak Children's Museum, Colorado Springs, CO

Designed and built custom WordPress theme

📞 352 348 2468

O 14805 Margaux Dr Clermont, FL 34714

linkedin.com/in/cmfnels

ChrisNelson-dev.com

Skills

HTML5 / XML

CSS3 / SASS

JavaScript / jQuery

Android Studio SDK

WordPress /

Magento / Java /

GIT / PHP / Ajax

Education

B.S. Computer Science Utah Valley University Orem, Utah / 2014